// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is a computer network?",
    answer: "A collection of interconnected computers and devices that can communicate and share resources",
    options: [
      "A type of software used to create documents and presentations",
      "A collection of interconnected computers and devices that can communicate and share resources",
      "A device used to display information on a computer screen",
      "The physical casing that protects a computerâ€™s internal components",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is internet?",
    answer: "Interconnection of wide area networks",
    options: [
      "A network of interconnected local area networks",
      "A collection of unrelated computers",
      "Interconnection of wide area networks",
      "A single network",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What is the full form of OSI? ",
    answer: "open system interconnection",
    options: [
      "optical service implementation",
      "open service Internet",
      "open system interconnection",
      "operating system interface",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "How many layers are there in the ISO OSI reference model?",
    answer: "7",
    options: [
      "5",
      "4",
      "7",
      "6",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What are nodes in a computer network?",
    answer: "all of the mentioned",
    options: [
      "the computer that routes the data",
      "the computer that terminates the data",
      "the computer that originates the data",
      "all of the mentioned",
    ]
  },
   {
     numb: 6,
     question: "Which one of the following is not a function of network layer?",
     answer: "error control",
     options: [
       "routing",
       "error control",
       "inter-networking",
       "congestion contro",
     ]
   },

   {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What is the term for an endpoint of an inter-process communication flow across a computer network?",
    answer: "socket",
    options: [
      "port",
      "machine",
      "socket",
      "pipe",
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question: " Which layer does the data link layer take packets from and encapsulate them into frames for transmission?",
    answer: "network layer",
    options: [
      "transport layer",
      "network layer",
      "physical layer",
      "application laye",
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which type of network shares the communication channel among all the machines?",
    answer: " 4GT Model",
    options: [
      "anycast network",
      "multicast network",
      "unicast network",
      "broadcast network",
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of the following maintains the Domain Name System?",
    answer: "distributed database system",
    options: [
      "a single server",
      "a single computer",
      "distributed database system",
      "none of the mentioned"
    ]
  },

]